All right, Phoebe?
If I were omnipotent for a day,
I would want world peace...
...no hunger, good things
for the rain forest.
And bigger boobs.
Well, see, you took mine.
What about you?
If I were omnipotent for a day,
I'd make myself omnipotent forever.
There's always one guy.
"lf I had a
wish, I'd wish for three more wishes. "
Hey, Joey.
What would you do
if you were omnipotent?
Probably kill myself.
Excuse me?
If little Joey's dead,
then I got no reason to live.
Joey, omnipotent.
You are?
Ross, l' m sorry. I had no idea. I
thought it was a theoretical question.
FRIENDS
How does she do that?
I can't sleep in a public place.
Would you look at her?
She is so peaceful.
What? What? What?
Hi.
It's okay. You just nodded off again.
What's going on?
I got no sleep last night.
My grandmother has a new boyfriend...
and they' re both kind of insecure
in bed,
so And deaf.
They reassure each other
that they' re having a good time.
You have no idea how loud they are.
You can stay with Rachel and me.
Gracias.
- 95, 96, 97.
See, I told you. Less than 100
steps
from our place to here.
You got way too much free time, man.
There's the birthday boy.
Ross, check it out!
Hockey tickets. Rangers-Penguins
tonight and we're taking you
Happy birthday, pal!
We love you, man.
It's funny.
My birthday
was seven months ago.
So?
So you had an extra ticket...
and couldn't decide
who
got to bring a date?
Well, aren't we
Mr. The-Glass-ls-Half-Empty?
Oh, my God!
Is today the 20th?
October 20th?
I hoped you wouldn't remember.
What's wrong with the 20th?
Eleven days before Halloween.
All the good costumes are gone?
Today's the day Carol and I first...
...consummated our...
... physical relationship.
Sex.
I better pass on the game.
I'm just gonna go home and think about
my ex-wife and her lesbian lover.
The hell with hockey!
Let's all do that!
Come on, Ross! You, me, Joey, ice!
Guys' night out!
Come on, what do you say, big guy?
What are you doing?
I have no idea.
Come on, Ross.
Maybe it will take my mind off it.
Promise to buy me a big foam finger?
You got it.
Look, look, look!
My first paycheck!
Look at the window!
There's my name!
Hi, me!
I remember when
I got my first paycheck.
There was a cave-in in a mine,
and eight people were killed.
You worked in a mine?
No, I worked at a Dairy Queen. Why?
Isn't this exciting? I earned this.
I wiped tables for it. I steamed milk.
And it was totally...
... not worth it.
What's FlCA?
Why's he getting all my money?
I mean, what?
Chandler, look at that.
This is not that bad.
You're fine, yeah, for a first job.
You can totally,
totally live on this.
By the way, great service today.
- Incredible!
- Excelent!
Hockey!
Rachel?
Oh, my God!
I swear I've seen birds
do this on Wild Kingdom.
What are you guys doing here?
Well, we were in the city shopping,
and your mom said you work here,
aaand it's true!
Look at you in the apron.
You look like you're in a play.
Look at you, you are so big I can't believe it!
I know. I know! I'm a duplex.
So what's going on with you?
Well, guess who my dad's
making partner in his firm?
And while we're on the subject of news..
Look, look, I have elbows!
...Poulet passes it up to Leetch!
Leetch spots Messier in the crease- there's the pass!
We'll take a brief time out while Messier
stops to look at some women's shoes.
Carol was wearing boots just like those
the night that we...
we first- y'know.
Fact, she, uh... she never took'em off,
'cause we... we...
Sorry. Sorry.
What?
Peach pit.
Yes, Bunny?
That night we, uh... we had...
Peaches?
Actually, nectarines, but basically...
Could've been a peach.
Then, uh, then we got dressed,
and I... I... I walked her to the...
...the bus stop...
I'm fine.
Hey, that woman's got an ass like Carol's!
What? Thought we were trying to find stuff.
So c'mon, you guys,
tell me all the dirt!
Well, the biggest news is still
you dumping Barry at the altar!
Alright. Let's talk reality for a second.
When are you coming home?
What?
Guys, I'm not.
C'mon, this is us.
I'm not!
This is what I'm doing now.
I've got this job...
Waitressing?
Okay, I'm not just waitressing.
I'm.. I, um...
I write the specials on the specials board,
I take the uh dead flowers
out of the vase...
Oh, and, um, sometimes Artelle lets me put
the little chocolate blobbies on the cookies.
Well. Your mom didn't tell
us about the blobbies.
Hey, Rach.
How was it with your friends?
Okay! How would you like some Tiki Death Punch?
What's that?
Weeeell, it's rum, and...
Okay.
We thought since Phoebe was staying over tonight
we'd have kinda like a slumber party thing.
We got some trashy magazines,
we got cookie dough, we got Twister...
Ooh! Ooh! And I brought Operation!
But, um, I lost the tweezers,
so we can't operate.
But we can prep the guy!
Uh, Rach, it's the Visa card people.
Oh, God, ask them what they want.
Could you please tell me
what this is in reference to?
Yes, hold on.
Um, they say there's been some
unusual activity on your account.
But I haven't used my card in weeks!
That is the unusual activity.
Look, they just wanna see if you're okay.
They wanna know if I'm okay. Okay..
they wanna know if I'm okay,
okay, let's see.
Well, let's see,
the FICA guys took all my money,
everyone I know is either getting married,
or getting pregnant,
or getting promoted,
and I'm getting coffee!
And it's not even for me!
So if that sounds like I'm okay, okay,
then you can tell them I'm okay, okay?
Uh... Rachel has left the building,
can you call back?
Alright, c'mon!
Let's play Twister!
Sorry, sorry...
Uh... oh.
What? There was ice
there that night with Carol?
Plastic seats?
Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans?
No, actually I was just saying it
looks like we're not sitting together.
But now you mention it,
there was ice there that night...
It was the first frost...
C'mon, sit. Just sit down, sit.
You should feel great about yourself!
You're doing this amazing independence thing!
Monica, what is so amazing?
I gave up, like, everything. And for what?
You are just like Jack.
...Jack from downstairs?
No, Jack and the Beanstalk.
Ah, the other Jack.
Yeah, right! See, he gave up something,
but then he got those magic beans.
And then he woke up, and there was this,
this big plant outside his window,
full of possibilities and stuff...
And he lived in a village,
and you live in the Village.
Okay, but Pheebs, Pheebs, Jack gave up  a cow,
I gave up an orthodontist.
Okay, I... I... I know, I know I didn't love him...
Oh, see, Jack did love the cow.
But see, it was a plan.
Y'know, it was clear.
It was figured out,
and now everything's just kinda like...
Floopy?
So what, you're not the only one.
I mean, half the time we don't know where we're going.
You've just gotta figure at some point
it's all gonna come together,
and it's just gonna be... un-floopy.
Oh, like that's a word.
Okay, but Monica, what if... what if it
doesn't come together? ...Pheebs?
Oh, well... 'cause.... you just... I don't like this question.
Okay, see, see, you guys,
what if we don't get magic beans?
I mean, what if all we've got are...
...beans?
Get him! GET HIM! Get him!
Get- YESSS!
Not laughing now, are ya pal!
See buddy, that's all you need, a bunch of
toothless guys hitting each other with sticks.
Pass it!
He's open!
Shoot! Shoot!
Shoot!
Hey, look, we're on that TV thing!
'Scuse me.
It says to call this number if you're not
completely satisfied with this candy bar.
Well, I'm not completely satisfied.
Listen, it's kind of an emergency.
Well, I guess you know that,
or we'd be in the predicament room.
Hold on.
Fill these out, sit over there.
Look, I don't wanna make any trouble,
okay,
but I'm in a lot of pain here, alright?
My face is dented.
Well, you'll have to wait your turn.
Well, how long do you think it'll be?
Any minute now.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
I didn't mean to bring you down.
No, you were right.
I don't have a plan.
Pizza guy!
Thank God.
Food.
Phoebe?
What?
Do you have a plan?
I don't even have a 'pl'.
Hi, one, uh, mushroom, green pepper and onion?
No, no, that's not what we ordered...
We ordered a fat-free
crust with extra cheese.
Wait, you're not 'G.Stephanopoulos?'
Man, my dad's gonna kill me!
Wait!
Did you say
..."G.Stephanopoulos"?
Yeah. This one goes across the street,
I must have given him yours.
Oh, bonehead, bonehead!
Wait, was this a-a small mediterranean
guy with curiously intelligent good looks?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Was he wearing a stunning blue suit?
And... and a power tie?
No, pretty much just a towel.
Oh God.
So you guys want me to take this back?
Are you nuts?!
We've got George Stephanopoulos' pizza!
Uh, Pheebs? Who's George Snuffalopagus?
Big Bird's friend.
I see pizza!
Oh, I wanna see! Lemme see! Lemme see!
Hello? Who are we spying on?
White House adviser?
Clinton's campaign guy?
The one with the great hair,
sexy smile, really cute butt?
Oh, him, the little guy? Oh, I love him!
Ooh, wait.. wait, I see a woman.
Please tell me it's his mother.
Definitely not his mother.
Oh, no...
Oh, wait, she's walking across the floor...
she's walking... she's walking...
she's going for the pizza...
Hey, that's not for you, bitch!
Excuse me,
look, we've been here for over an hour,
and a lot of people less sick than my friend have gone in.
I mean, that guy with the toe thing?
Who's he sleeping with?
Oh, c'mon Dora, don't be mad...
I know we both said some things
we didn't mean,
but that doesn't mean we still don't love each other.
Y'know, I feel like I've lost her...
Light still out?
Yeah.
Oh. Maybe they're... napping.
Oh please, they're having sex.
Shut up!
So, whaddya think George is like?
I think he's shy.
Yeah. I think you have to draw him out.
And then... when you do...
he's a preppy animal.
I remember the moonlight
coming through the window...
and her face had the most
incredible glow.
Yes, the moon, the glow,
the magical feeling,
you did this part... Could I get some
painkillers over here, please?
He's right, enough, already. What is the big deal about today?
So you slept with her for
the first time, so what?
You slept with her for
seven years after that.
Look, it's just a little
more complicated...
Well, what? What? What is it?
That she left you? That she likes women?
That she left you for another woman that likes women?
Little louder, okay, I think there's a man on the
twelfth floor in a coma that didn't quite hear you...
Then what?
My first time with Carol
was...
What?
It was my first...
time.
With Carol?
So in your whole life,
you've only been with one...
Whoah, boy, hockey was a big mistake!
There was a whole bunch of stuff
we could've done tonight!
Okay. Okay, I got one.
Do you remember that vegetarian pate
that I made that you loved so much?
Well, unless goose is a vegetable...
ha haaaah!
Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with Jason Hurley.
What?! You slept with Jason?
You'd already broken up.
How long?
A couple hours.
Oh, that's nice!
Okay, okay, okay, I got one!
Anyway...
The valentine Tommy Rollerson
left in your locker was really from me.
Excuse me?!
Hello? Like he was really
gonna send you one?
She was a big girl.
Really. Well, at least 'big girls'
don't pee in their pants in seventh grade!
I was laughing! You made me laugh!
There he is! There he is!
Where?
Right... where we've been looking all night!
He is so cute!
Oh, George, baby, drop the towel!
Yeah, drop it! Drop the towel!
Please drop the…
Man. Can you believe he's
only had sex with one woman?
I think it's great.
Y'know, it's sweet,
it's romantic...
Really?
No, you kidding? The guy's a freak...
Hey, buddy.
Hi.
Oh, that's attractive.
Oh, I thought you were
great in Silence of the Lambs.
Oh come on, admit it!
All things considered, you had fun tonight.
Fun? Where was the fun?
Tell me specifically, which part was the fun part?
Where's my puck?
Oh, ah... the kid has it.
The kid...?
Excuse me, uh, that's, that's my puck.
I found it.
Finders keepers, losers weepers.
You gotta do it, man.
Oh yeah? Well, I'm rubber,
you're glue, whatever...
can't do it.
Listen, uh... gimme back my puck.
Sí, claro que sí.
'Yes', how about. C'mere. Gimme!
No! No!
Hey! Hey! No rough holding in my ER!
GIVE ME MY PUCK!!
Now that was fun.
Okay, Right foot red.
Could've played Monopoly,
but nooooo.
Thanks.
Okay, Pheebs: Right hand blue.
Good.
Hello?
Oh, uh, Rachel, it's the Visa card people.
Oh, okay. Will you take my place?
Alright.
Yes, this is Rachel.
Hello? Oh, yeah, no, I know,
I... I haven't been using it much.
Oh, well, thanks, but, I'm okay, really.
Green. To the green.
I've got magic beans.
Never... never mind.
To the left, to the left... aww!
Ohhh... I'm fine.
www.tvsubtitles.net