No, no, we're done!
The One With the Dozen Lasagnas
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Aunt Silv, stop yelling!
If you'd told me
vegetarian lasagna. . .
. . .I would've made
vegetarian lasagna.
The meat's only every third layer.
Maybe you could scrape.
Ross, did you really read
all these baby books?
You could plunk me down in
any woman's uterus, no compass. . .
. . .and I could find my way
out like that!
This is cool.
It says in some parts of the world
people eat the placenta.
And we're done with the yogurt.
Sorry.
Aunt Silv, I did this as a favor.
I am not a caterer.
What do you want me to do
with a dozen lasagnas?
Nice talk, Aunt Silv.
You kiss Uncle Freddie
with that mouth?
Ross, listen.
Do you know that right now
your baby is only this big?
This is your baby.
''Hi, Daddy. ''
Hello.
''How come you don't live with Mommy?''
''How come Mommy lives
with that other lady?''
''What's a lesbian?''
Honey, you can say it.
It's Poconos. Poconos.
It's like ''poke a nose. ''
Poke a nose.
So did I hear ''Poconos''?
My sister's giving us her place
for the weekend.
First weekend away together.
-Yeah, it's a big step.
-I know.
It's just a weekend.
Big deal.
Wasn't this supposed to be
just a fling?
Shouldn't it be. . .
. . .flung by now?
We are way past the ''fling'' thing.
I'm feeling things I've only
read about in Danielle Steel books.
When I'm with him,
I'm just totally, totally. . . .
Nauseous.
I'm physically nauseous.
What am I supposed to do?
Call Immigration?
I could call Immigration.
I love babies with
their little baby shoes. . .
. . .and their little baby toes
and their little hands. . . .
You're gonna have to stop that. . .
. . .forever.
Need a new table.
You think?
-Come on in.
-Hello.
I brought the books. . .
. . .and Monica sends her love
along with this lasagna.
Great!
Is it vegetarian?
Because Susan doesn't eat meat.
I'm pretty sure that it is.
So I got the results
of the amnio today.
Tell me.
Is everything. . .?
Totally and completely healthy.
That's great! That is great!
When did you and Susan
meet Huey Lewis?
That's our friend Tanya.
Of course, it's your friend Tanya.
Don't you wanna know
about the sex?
The sex?
I'm having enough trouble with
the image of you and Susan together.
But when you throw in Tanya. . . .
The sex of the baby, Ross.
You know it?
Do you want to know?
I don't want to know.
Absolutely not.
I think you shouldn't know until
you look down there. . .
. . .and see,
''Oh, there it is. . . ''
. . .or isn't.
-Hello, Ross.
-Susan.
So?
So did you hear?
Yes, we did.
Everything's A-OK.
Oh, that's so cool!
It really is.
Do we know?
We certainly do.
It's going to be a--
Hello?
A guy who doesn't wanna know
is standing here.
Well, is it what
we thought it would be?
What. . .?
What did we think it'd be?
I don't want to know.
Don't want to know.
I should probably just go.
-Well, thanks for the books.
-No problem.
Susan.
Who should we call first?
Your folks or Deb and Rhona?
Never mind.
I don 't wanna know.
So just because it was my table,
I have to buy a new one?
That's the rule.
What rule?
There's no rule.
If anything, you owe me a table.
How did you get that?
This piece of furniture
was fine. . .
. . .until your breakfast adventure
with Angela Delveccio.
You knew about that?
The impressions you made in the butter
left little to the imagination.
How about if we split it?
What do you mean,
like, buy it together?
Do you think we're ready for that?
Why not?
It's a big commitment.
What if one of us wants to move out?
-Are you moving out?
-I'm not moving out.
You'd tell me if you were?
-It's just, with my last roommate--
-I know all about Kip.
We bought a hibachi together,
then he ran off and got married. . .
. . .and things got ugly.
Let me ask you something.
Was Kip a better roommate than me?
Don't do that.
You've got a couple changes
in your schedule.
Your 4:00 herbal massage
has been pushed back to 4:30.
And Ms. Summerfield
canceled her 5:30 shiatsu.
Thanks.
Here comes your 3:00.
I don't mean to sound
unprofessional, but-- Yum!
Paolo! Hi!
What are you doing here?
Rachella tell me you. . .
. . .massage?
Well, Rachella's right.
I don't know what you said,
so let's start.
I am. . .
. . .being naked?
That's your decision.
Some people prefer to take off--
Being naked!
I can't believe you don't want to know.
I couldn't not know.
If the doctor knows,
and Carol knows, and Susan knows--
And Monica knows.
How could you?
I don't even know.
Carol called to thank me
for the lasagna.
I asked. She told me.
So what's it going to be?
Great! Now he knows
and I don't know.
I'm sorry. I'm excited
about being an aunt.
Or an uncle.
Fine!
What's the matter?
Nothing! I'm sorry.
I'm just, I'm out of sorts.
Can we get some
cappuccino over here?
Oh, right! That's me!
That table place closes at 7. Come on.
Fine.
What is it?
You know Paolo?
I'm familiar with his work.
He made a move on me.
-The store'll be open tomorrow.
-More coffee.
What happened?
He came in for a massage. . .
...and everything was fine until....
My God!
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah. I'm sure.
And all of a sudden, his hands
weren't the problem anymore.
Was it. . .?
Boy Scouts could've
camped under there.
''Ooh,'' what?
--ma Thurman.
-The actress!
-Uma Thurman!
Thanks, Rach.
-What'll you do?
-You have to tell her.
You have to! It's your
moral obligation as a friend. . .
. . .as a woman.
It's a feminist issue.
Guys? Guys?
You have to tell her.
Feminist issue?
That's where I went.
She is gonna hate me!
Will you pick one?
Just pick one.
Here, how about that one?
That's patio furniture.
So what?
Like people will come in and think,
''Uh-oh, I'm outside again. ''
Fine.
What about the birds?
I don't know.
Birds just don't say. . .
. . . ''Hello, sit here. Eat something. ''
You pick one.
How about the ladybugs?
So forget about the birds, but
big red insects suggest fine dining?
Fine! Do you want the birds?
Get the birds!
Not like that, I won't.
Kip would've liked the birds.
Hi, Pheebs.
Are you moving out?
No, these aren't all
of my suitcases.
This one's Paolo's.
Rachel, can we talk for a sec?
Sure.
Just for a sec, because Paolo's
on his way over.
We haven't known each other
for that long a time.
There are three things
you should know about me.
One, my friends are the most
important thing in my life.
Two, I never lie.
And three, I make the best
oatmeal raisin cookies in the world.
Thanks, Pheebs.
My God!
Why have I never tasted these before?
I don't make them a lot, because
it's not fair to the other cookies.
You're right. These are
the best oatmeal raisin cookies.
Which proves that I never lie.
I guess you don't.
Paolo made a pass at me.
So what do you think?
It's the most beautiful table
I've ever seen.
I know.
So will you balance the plates
on these little heads?
Who cares?
We'll eat at the sink.
Come on!
Heads up, Ross.
Score!
You suck!
Are you okay?
I need some milk.
I've got milk.
Here you go.
Better?
I feel so stupid!
I think about the other day
with you guys.
And I was all,
''Oh, Paolo! He's so great!
He makes me feel so--''
God!
I'm so embarrassed!
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm the one he hit on.
Phoebe, I pushed him on you.
If I had never met him,
this would never--
-I'm so sorry.
-No, I'm sorry.
Wait!
-What are we sorry about?
-I don't know.
Right. He's the pig.
-Such a pig!
-Oh, God, he's such a pig!
He's like a big disgusting pig. . . .
-Pig man!
-Yes, good!
But he was my pig man!
How did I not see this?
Oh, I know!
Because. . .
. . .he's gorgeous.
And he's charming.
And the way he looks at you--
The end.
God!
Should I not have told you?
Trust me, it's much better
that I know.
But I just liked it better before.
It was better.
I think she took it pretty well.
Paolo's over there right now, so. . . .
We should go
and see if she's okay.
Just one second.
Score!
Game! Us!
Come on.
It looks like
we kicked your butts.
She kicked our butts.
You could be on the Olympic
''Standing There'' team.
Come on. Two on one.
Why are you still here?
She just broke up with him.
It's time for you to swoop in.
What, now?
Now is when you swoop.
When Paolo walks out of there,
you gotta be the first guy she sees.
She's got to know
you're everything he's not.
You're like the anti-Paolo.
My Catholic friend is right.
She's distraught.
You're there for her.
You pick up the pieces, and then
you usher in. . .
. . . ''The Age of Ross. ''
Hold it! Ascolta!
-How's it going?
-Don't stare.
She finished throwing
his clothes off the balcony.
Now there's just
gesturing and arm-waving.
That is either, ''How could you?''
or ''Enormous breasts! ''
Here he comes.
I am. . .
. . .to say goodbye.
Okay, bye-bye.
I hate you
for what you did to Rachel.
But I still have five of these. . .
. . .so heat it at 375
untiI the cheese bubbles.
I just wanna tell you. . .
. . .and I think I'd speak
for everyone when I say. . . .
Just look at her.
Guys, I think only one of us
should go out there. . .
-. . .so she's not overwhelmed.
-Right.
And I really think it should be me.
You all right?
I've been better.
Come here.
Listen. . .
. . .you deserve
so much better than him.
I mean, you. . .
. . .you should be with a guy who knows
what he has when he has you.
What?
I'm so sick of guys!
I don't want to look
at another guy.
I don't want to think
about another guy.
I don't even want
to be near another guy.
Ross, you're so great.
-Are you all right?
-Are you okay?
Medium.
Any cookies left?
See, Rach. . .
. . .I don't think swearing off guys
altogether is the answer.
What you need is to develop a more
sophisticated screening process.
I just need to be
by myself for a while.
I just gotta
figure out what I want.
See, because not all guys out there
are gonna be a Paolo.
No, I know. I know.
And I'm sure your little boy's
not gonna grow up to be one.
What?
I'm having a boy?
No. In fact,
you're not having a boy.
I'm having a boy.
Am I having a boy?
You're having a boy!
I'm having a boy!
-What?
-What is it?
I'm having a boy!
We already knew that!
I'm having a son.
And that would be a shutdown!
Shutout!
Where you guys going?
Come on, one more game!
It's 2:30 in the morning.
Get out!
You guys are always hanging out
in my apartment.
Come on, I'll only use
my left hand.
Come on, wussies!
All right! Okay!
I gotta go!
I'm going.
And I'm gone.
One more game?
www.tvsubtitles.net