Terry, I know I haven't
worked here long. . .
. . .but I was wondering,
would it be possible. . .
. . .if I got a $ 100 advance
on my salary?
An advance?
So that I can spend
Thanksgiving with my family.
Every year we ski in Vail, and
my father pays for my ticket. . .
. . .but I've started
this whole independent thing. . .
. . .which is actually why
I took this ''job. ''
Rachel, Rachel, sweetheart!
You're a terrible, terrible waitress.
Really, really awful.
I hear what you're saying.
I'm with you.
But I'm trying really hard,
and I think I'm doing better.
I really do.
Does anybody need coffee?
The One Where Underdog Gets Away
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Excuse me, sir?
You come in here all the time.
I was wondering. . .
. . .is there a possibility that
you could advance me my tips?
That's fine.
Sorry about that spill before!
Only 98.50 to go!
Did you know Mom and Dad are going
to Puerto Rico for Thanksgiving?
What? No, they're not.
The Blymans invited them.
You're wrong.
I am not wrong.
No, I just talked to them.
I'm calling Mom.
And this from the Cry for Help
Department: Are you wearing makeup?
Yes, I am. As of today, I'm officially
''Joey Tribbiani: actor/model. ''
I was thinking you
look more like ''Joey Tribbiani. . .
. . .man/woman. ''
What were you modeling?
You know those posters for
the City Free Clinic?
So you're gonna be one of those
healthy, healthy, healthy guys?
The asthma guy's really cute.
Know which one you're gonna be?
But I hear Lyme disease is open, so. . . .
Good luck, man. I hope you get it.
Thanks.
You were right.
How can they do this to us?
It's Thanksgiving!
How about if I cook dinner at my place?
I'll make it just like Mom's.
Will you make the mashed potatoes
with the lumps?
They're not actually supposed to--
I'll work on the lumps.
Joey, you're going home, right?
Chandler, you're still boycotting
all the pilgrim holidays?
Yes. Every single one of them.
-Phoebe, you'll be with your grandma?
-And her boyfriend.
But we're celebrating Thanksgiving
in December because he's lunar.
So you're free Thursday, then?
Yeah. Oh, can I come?
Rach, you still going to Vail?
Absolutely. Shoop, shoop, shoop!
Only $ 1 02 to go.
I thought it was 98.50?
Well, it was, but I broke a cup.
Well, I'm off to Carol's.
Ooh, ooh, why don't we invite her?
Ooh, ooh, because she's my ex-wife. . .
. . .and will probably want to bring
her ooh, ooh, lesbian life-partner.
Is Carol here?
No, she's at a faculty meeting.
I just came by to pick up my skull.
Well, not mine, but. . . .
Come in.
Carol borrowed it for a class, and I
have to get it back to the museum.
What's it look like?
Kind of like a big face without skin.
I'm familiar with the concept.
You can just look for it.
You guys sure have a lot of books
about being a lesbian.
You know, you have to take a course.
Otherwise they don't let you do it.
Yertle the Turtle!
A classic.
Actually, I'm reading it to the baby.
The baby that hasn't been born yet?
Wouldn't that mean you're. . .
. . .crazy?
What? You don't think they can
hear sounds in there?
You're not serious? I mean. . .
. . .you really talk to it?
Yeah, all the time.
I want the baby to know my voice.
Do you talk about me?
All the time.
Really?
We just refer to you
as ''Bobo, the sperm guy. ''
If she's talking to it, I just think
I should get some belly-time too.
Not that I believe any of this.
I believe it. I think the baby can
totally hear everything.
I'll show you.
This will seem a little weird.
But you put your head
inside this turkey. . .
. . .and we'll all talk and you'll
hear everything we say.
I'd just like to say I'm totally
behind this experiment.
In fact, I'd very much like
to butter your head.
-Did you make your money?
-Not even close.
Forget Vail.
Forget seeing my family.
Forget shoop, shoop, shoop.
Here's your mail.
Thanks. You can just
put it on the table.
Here's your mail!
Thanks. You can just
put it on the table!
Would you just open it!
Oh, my God!
You guys are great!
We all chipped in.
We did?
You owe me $20.
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Chandler, here you go.
Your traditional holiday feast.
Tomato soup. . .
. . .grilled-cheese fixings and
your family-size bag of Funyuns.
This is your Thanksgiving dinner?
What is it with you
and this holiday?
I'm 9 years old.
I hate this story!
We've just finished
Thanksgiving dinner.
I have-- I remember
this part vividly--
--a mouthful of pumpkin pie.
And this is the moment my parents
tell me they're getting divorced.
Oh, my God!
Very difficult to enjoy Thanksgiving
dinner once you've seen it in reverse.
We used to work together.
We did?
At Macy's. You're
the Obsession girl, right?
I was the Aramis guy.
Aramis? Aramis?
Yeah, right!
You're the best in the business.
-Get out!
-I'm serious!
You're amazing! You know when to
spritz. You know when to lay back.
Really? You don't know
what that means to me.
You smell great tonight.
What are you wearing?
Nothing.
Listen, do you wanna go get a drink?
Yeah, that would be--
-What's wrong?
-I remembered I have to do something.
What?
Leave.
Wait, wait, wait!
I guess you all saw it.
Saw what?
We're just laughing. You know
how laughter can be infectious.
Set another place for Thanksgiving.
My entire family thinks I have VD.
''Tonight, on a very special Blossom. ''
Looking good! Okay!
Cider's mulling, turkey's
turking, yams are yamming. . . .
What?
I don't know. It's just not
the same without Mom in the kitchen.
That's it. Get out of
my way and stop annoying me!
Well, that's closer.
I got the tickets!
Five hours from now,
shoop, shoop, shoop!
Oh, you must stop shooping.
I'm gonna get my stuff.
Will you just come in, already?
I prefer to keep a safe distance
from all this merriment.
Look out! Incoming pumpkin pie!
We all laughed when you did it with
the stuffing, but that's not funny.
Monica, I got a question.
I don't see any Tater Tots.
That's not a question.
But my mom always makes them.
It's a tradition.
A piece of turkey on your fork,
a little cranberry sauce and a Tot!
I mean it's. . .
. . .bad enough I can't be with
my family, because of my disease.
All right. Fine.
Tonight's potatoes will be both
mashed with lumps. . .
. . .and in the form of Tots.
I'm off to talk to my unborn child.
Mom never hit.
Okay, all done.
Phoebe, did you whip the pota--?
Ross needs lumps!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I just--
I thought we could have them whipped
and then add some peas and onions.
Why would we do that?
Then they'd be like
my mom used to make it. . .
. . .before she died.
Three kinds of potatoes coming up.
Goodbye, you guys!
Thanks for everything!
Oh, God, look at-- Sorry!
I'm so sorry.
The most unbelievable thing has
happened! Underdog has gotten away!
The balloon?
No, the actual cartoon character.
Of course the balloon!
It's all over the news.
He broke free and was spotted
over Washington Square Park.
I'm going to the roof.
Who's with me?
I can't. I gotta go!
An 80-foot dog loose over the city?
How often does that happen?
Almost never.
Got the keys?
Anytime you're ready!
Okay, here we go.
Where am I talking to here?
There is one way that seems to offer
a certain acoustical advantage, but. . . .
Just aim for the bump.
Okay, here goes.
You know, I can't do this.
It's too weird. I feel stupid.
It's fine. You don't have to do it
just because Susan does it.
Hello, baby!
--the moment we first saw the giant dog
shadow fall over the park!
But did they have to shoot him down?
That was just mean.
Right about now the turkey should
be crispy on the outside. . .
. . .and juicy on the inside.
Why are we standing here?
We're waiting for you to open
the door. You've got the keys.
No, I don't.
Yes, you do. When we left,
you said, ''Got the keys. ''
No, I didn't. I asked. . .
. . . ''Got the keys?''
You said, ''Got the keys! ''
Either of you have the keys?
The oven is on!
I've gotta get my ticket!
Wait! We have a copy of your key.
Then get it!
That tone won't make me go any faster.
That one will.
And everyone's telling me,
''You gotta pick a major! ''
So on a dare, I picked paleontology.
And you have no idea what I'm saying,
because, let's face it, you're a fetus.
You're just happy you don't
have gills anymore.
You don't have to talk to it.
You can sing to it.
Please. I am not singing
to your stomach.
How's it going?
Here we come
Walking down the street
Get the funniest looks from
Everyone we meet
Hey, hey--
-Did you feel that?
-I did.
-Does it always--?
-That was the first!
Keep singing! Keep singing!
Hey, hey, you're my baby
And I can 't wait to meet you
When you come out I'll buy you a bagel
And then we'll go to the zoo
I felt it that time!
Hey, hey, I'm your daddy
I'm the one without any breasts
Not that one.
Can you go any faster?
I got one keyhole and a zillion keys!
You do the math.
Why do you guys have so many
keys in there anyway?
For an emergency just like this.
All right. Listen, smirky!
If it wasn't for your stupid balloon. . .
. . .I'd be on a plane watching a woman
do this right now. But I'm not!
I swear you said you had the keys!
I wouldn't say I had the
keys unless I had the keys!
I obviously did not have the keys!
That's it! Enough with the keys.
No one say ''keys'' !
Why would I have the keys!
Besides the fact that
you said you did?
-But I didn't!
-Well, you should have.
-Why?
-Because!
Because everything's
my responsibility?
Isn't it enough that I'm making
Thanksgiving dinner?
Everyone wants a different potato,
so I'm making different potatoes.
Does anybody care what kind
of potatoes I want?
Just as long as Phoebe gets
her peas and onions. . .
. . .and Mario gets his Tots.
It's my first Thanksgiving, and I--
It's all burnt, and I can't. . . .
Monica, only dogs can hear you now.
Look, the door's open!
Here we go.
The turkey's burnt!
Potatoes are ruined! Potatoes
are ruined! Potatoes are ruined!
Here we come
Walking down the--
This doesn't smell like Mom's.
It doesn't, does it?
But you wanted lumps.
Well, here you go, buddy.
You got one!
God, this is great!
The plane is gone, so I guess
I'm stuck here with you guys.
We all had better plans, okay?
This was nobody's first choice!
Oh, really?
So why was I busting my ass
to make this delicious dinner?
You call that delicious?
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Now, this feels like Thanksgiving.
What?
Ugly Naked Guy's taking
his turkey out of the oven.
Oh, my God! He's not alone.
Ugly Naked Guy. . .
. . .is having Thanksgiving
dinner with Ugly Naked Gal.
I gotta see this!
All right, Ugly Naked Guy!
Ugly naked dancing!
It's nice that he has someone.
Shall I carve?
By all means.
Who wants light cheese,
and who wants dark cheese?
I don't even want to know
about the dark cheese.
-Does anybody want to split this?
-I will.
You guys have to make a wish.
Make a wish?
Come on, you know, Thanksgiving.
You got the bigger half!
What did you wish for?
The bigger half.
All right, I'd like to
propose a toast.
A little toast here. Ding, ding!
This isn't exactly the kind of
Thanksgiving you planned. . .
. . .but for me this has
been really great.
I think because it didn't
involve divorce. . .
. . .or projectile vomiting.
If you had gone to Vail. . .
. . .or if you had been with your
family, or if you didn't have. . .
. . .syphilis and stuff. . .
. . .we wouldn't be
all together.
So I guess what I'm trying
to say is. . .
. . .I'm very thankful that all
of your Thanksgivings sucked.
-That's so sweet!
-Thank you.
Here's to a lousy Christmas!
And a crappy New Year!
www.tvsubtitles.net