-I'm sorry!
-Oh, my God! That's it!
You just barge in here
and you don't knock?
You have no respect
for my privacy?
-Rachel, wait!
-No, you wait!
Can I just say one thing?
What?! What?
That's a relatively open weave
and I can still see your. . .
. . .nippular area.
The One With the Boobies
English Subtitles by
GELULA & CO., INC.
Honey, honey. . .
. . .tell them the story about
your patient. . .
. . .who thinks things are
other things.
Like when the phone rings
and she takes a shower. . . .
That's pretty much it.
But you tell it really well, sweetie.
Thanks.
Now go away so we can
talk about you.
Okay. I'll miss you.
Isn't he great?
He's so cute. And he
likes you so much.
I know. I know.
He's so sweet.
And so complicated, you know?
And for a shrink,
he's not too shrinky. You know?
Think you'll do it on his couch?
I don't know. That's a little weird.
It's vinyl. . . .
You guys want anything else?
-Could I have--
-We're all out.
Anybody else?
Did I miss something?
No, she's still upset
because I saw her boobies.
What were you doing
seeing her boobies?
It was an accident.
I wasn't across the street with
a telescope and a box of doughnuts.
Can we change the subject, please?
Because, hello? These aren't her
''boobies. '' These are her breasts.
Pheebs, I was hoping
for more of a change.
I don't know why you're embarrassed.
They were very nice boobies.
''Nice''?
They were ''nice''?
That's it?
I mean, mittens are ''nice. ''
Rock, hard place. . .
. . .me.
You're so funny!
He's really funny!
I wouldn't want to be there when
the laughter stops.
Back up there, sparky.
What did you mean by that?
It seems that maybe
you have intimacy issues. . .
. . .that you use your humor
to keep people at a distance.
I mean, I just met you.
I don't know you from Adam.
Only child, right?
Parents divorced
before you hit puberty.
How did you know?
It's textbook.
Hey, you guys.
You all know my dad, right?
-How long are you in the city?
-Two days.
I got a job midtown.
I'm better off
staying with the kid. . .
. . .than going back and forth
on the ferry.
I don't know this one.
This is my friend Roger.
-Good to meet you.
-You too.
What happened to the puppet guy?
Dad!
Excuse me.
So, Ross, how's the wife?
0 for 2, huh?
Chandler, quick,
say something funny!
Gotta go.
I miss you too.
I love you,
but it's getting late now--
Let me say hi. Hey, Ma!
Listen, I made the appointment
with Dr. Bassida and--
Excuse me?
Did you know this isn't Ma?
Her name's Ronni.
She's a pet mortician.
Sure.
So how long have you been. . . .
Remember when you were a kid, we'd
go see the big ships in the navy yard?
Since then?
No, it's only been six years.
I wanted to give you
a nice memory. . .
. . .so you'd know I wasn't always
such a terrible guy.
Joe, have you ever been in love?
I don't know.
Then you haven't.
You're burning your tomatoes.
You're one to talk.
Your dad's in love, bigtime.
And the worst part is,
it's with two different women.
Oh, man! Please tell me
one of them is Ma.
Of course one of them's Ma.
What's the matter with you?
It's like if you woke up one day
and found out. . .
. . .your dad was
leading this double life.
He's like actually some spy
working for the CIA.
That'd be cool!
This blows!
I know. Why can't parents
just stay parents?
Why do they
have to become people?
Why do they have--
Why. . .
. . .can't you stop staring
at my breasts?
What?
Didn't you get a good enough
look the other day?
We're all adults here.
There's only one way
to resolve this.
Since you saw her boobies. . .
. . .you're gonna have to show her
your pee-pee.
You know,
I don't see that happening.
Come on. He's right.
Tit for tat.
Well I'm not showing you my tat!
-It's Phoebe.
-And Rog!
Come on up.
Oh, good! Rog is here!
-What's the matter with Rog?
-Nothing. It's a little thing.
I hate that guy!
What? So he was a little analytical.
That's what he does.
Come on, he's not that bad.
That's where you're wrong!
Why would I marry her. . .
. . .if I thought on any level
that she was a lesbian?
I don't know.
Maybe you wanted
your marriage to fail.
Why? Why would I?
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe low self-esteem?
Maybe to compensate
for overshadowing a sibling.
Wait!
Go back to that ''sibling'' thing.
Well, I don't know.
It's conceivable that
you sabotaged your marriage. . .
. . .so the sibling would be less
of a failure in the parents' eyes.
That's ridiculous!
I don't feel guilty for her failures.
-So you think I'm a failure?
-Isn't he good?
That's not what I was saying.
I thought you were on my side. . .
. . .but maybe you were
sucking up to Mom and Dad. . .
. . .so they'd favor you.
I married a lesbian
to make you look good!
You're right.
I mean, you're right!
It wasn't just the Weebles,
but it was the Weeble Play Palace. . .
. . .and the Weeble's Cruise Ship. . .
. . .which had this little lifeboat
for the Weebles to wobble in.
That's tough, tough stuff.
Pheebs, if we're gonna
catch that movie, we gotta go.
Feel better, okay?
We're gonna be late, sweetie.
Thanks for everything, Mon.
No problem.
It was great seeing you again.
Mon, easy on those cookies, okay?
Remember, they're just food. . .
. . .they're not love.
I hate that guy!
Good night, you guys.
Oh, look!
It's the woman we ordered.
Can we help you?
No, thanks. I'm just waiting
for Joey Tribbiani.
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
Oh, no, not you. Big Joey.
Oh, my God!
You're so much cuter than
your pictures.
I'm Ronni.
Cheese nip?
Joey's having an embolism. . .
. . .but I'd go for a nip.
Most people,
when their pets pass on. . .
. . .want them laid out
like they're sleeping.
Occasionally you get a person
who wants them in a pose.
Like chasing their tail.
Or jumping to catch a Frisbee.
Joey, if I go first, I want to be
looking for my keys.
That's a good one!
Hey, Dad. Ronni's here.
Hello, babe!
What are you doing here?
You left your hair
at my place.
I thought you'd need it
for your meeting.
Thank you.
So! Who's up for a big
game of Kerplunk?
Look, I. . . .
I shouldn't have come.
I gotta go.
I'll miss the last train.
I don't want you taking
that thing this late.
Where am I gonna stay?
Here?
We'll go to a hotel.
-No, you won't.
-No, we won't.
If you go to a hotel,
you'll be doing stuff.
I want you right here,
where I can keep an eye on you.
You're gonna keep an eye on us?
Right, mister!
I don't care how old you are,
while you're here. . .
. . .you're gonna live by my rules.
And that means no sleeping
with your girlfriend.
Wow, he's strict.
Dad, you'll be in my room.
Ronni, you can stay in
Chandler's room.
Thanks.
You're a good kid.
Come on.
I'll show you to my room.
That sounds weird when it's not
followed by, ''No, thanks, it's late! ''
This is just for tonight.
Starting tomorrow, you gotta change.
-Six years is long enough!
-What kind of change?
-Break up with Ronni--
-I can't!
Then come clean with Ma!
This is not right!
I don't wanna hear it!
Now go to my room!
Hey, kickie!
What are you doing?
Trying to get comfortable.
-I can't sleep in my underwear.
-Well, you're gonna.
I've been thinking. . .
. . .about how I'm always
seeing girls on top of girls. . . .
Are they end-to-end,
or tall, like pancakes?
You know what I mean.
How I date all these women.
I always figured, when
the right one comes along. . .
. . .I'll be able to be a standup guy
and go the distance.
Now I'm looking at my Dad thinking--
You're not him, you're you.
When they wanted you to go into
your father's business, did you cave?
You chose
the out-of-work-actor business.
That wasn't easy, but you did it.
And I believe that
when the right woman comes along. . .
. . .you'll have the guts to say:
''No thanks, I'm married. ''
You really think so?
I really do.
-Thanks, Chandler.
-Get off!
May I help you?
Joey said I could use your shower
since Chandler's in ours.
Who are you?
Oh, I'm Ronni. Ronni Rapalono.
The mistress?
-Come on in.
-Thanks.
I'm Rachel.
Bathroom's up there.
Say, Ronni. . . .
How long has Chandler been
in the shower?
Like five minutes.
Perfect.
Fasten your seat belts. . .
. . .it's pee-pee time!
Hey, Mr. Trib.
Good morning, dear.
Chandler Bing,
it's time to see your thing.
-What's with you?
-I thought it was Chandler!
You were supposed to be in there
so I could see your thing!
Sorry, my thing
was in there with me.
How's it going?
Good.
Roger's having a dinner thing
and he wanted me to invite you guys.
What's going on?
Nothing.
It's just that. . . .
It's Roger.
There's something about--
Basically, we just feel
that he's. . . .
We hate that guy!
We hate him!
We're sorry, Pheebs.
Don't you think maybe it's just that
he's so perceptive. . .
. . .that it freaked you out?
-No, I hate him!
-No, we hate him!
I'm sorry.
Ma! What are you doing here?
I came to give you this. . .
. . .and this!
Big ring!
Why did you fill your father's head
with that garbage. . .
. . .about making things right?
Things were fine the way they were!
There's chicken in there.
Put it away.
For God's sake, Joey!
Really.
Hold on. You knew?
Of course I knew.
What do you think?
Your father is no James Bond.
You should have heard
his cover stories.
''I'm sleeping over at
my accountant's. ''
I mean, what is that?
Please!
So then, how could you--?
Do you remember
how your father used to be?
Always yelling.
Nothing made him happy.
Not that wood shop, not those
stupid little ships in the bottle.
Now he's happy.
I mean, it's nice.
He has a hobby.
Ma, I don't mean
to be disrespectful, but. . .
. . .what the hell
are you saying?
-I mean, what about you?
-Me? I'm fine.
Look, honey. . .
. . .in an ideal world. . .
. . .there'd be no her and your father
would look like Sting.
And I'll tell you something else:
Ever since that
poodle-stuffer came along. . .
. . .he's been so ashamed of himself
that he's been more attentive.
He's been more loving.
It's like every day is
our anniversary.
I'm happy for you. . .?
Well, don't be!
Because now everything's screwed up.
I just want it the way it was.
Ma, I'm sorry.
I just did what
I thought you'd want.
I know you did, cookie.
I know you did.
So tell me. . . .
Did you see her?
You're ten times prettier
than she is.
That's sweet.
Could I take her?
With this ring, no contest!
-What's wrong, sweetie?
-Nothing. . . .
What's wrong? Come on.
It's nothing. I'm fine.
It's just--
It's my friends.
They have a liking problem with you. . .
. . .in that. . .
. . .they don't.
They don't?
But you know. . .
. . .they don't see all
of the wonderfulness that I see.
They don't see all the good stuff
and all the sweet stuff.
They think you're a little. . . .
What?
Intense and creepy.
But I don't. Me, Phoebe.
I'm not at all surprised
they feel that way.
You're not?
That's why you're so great.
Actually, it's
quite typical behavior. . .
. . .when you have this kind
of dysfunctional group dynamic.
You know, this kind of codependent. . .
. . .emotionally stunted. . .
. . .sitting in your stupid coffeehouse,
with your stupid big cups. . .
. . .which, I'm sorry, might as well
have nipples on them.
And you're all like,
''Oh, define me! Define me!
Love me! I need love! ''
So you talked to your dad?
He's gonna keep cheating on Ma,
like she wanted.
Ma's gonna keep pretending
she doesn't know.
And my sister Tina
can't see her husband anymore. . .
. . .because he got
a restraining order.
Which has nothing to do with it,
except that I found out today.
Things have changed here
on Walton's mountain.
So Joey, are you okay?
Yeah, I guess.
It's just--
You know, they're parents.
After a certain point,
you gotta let go.
Even if you know better. . .
. . .you gotta let them make
their own mistakes.
And just think. . .
. . .in a few years,
we'll turn into them.
Oh, please!
If I turn into my parents,
I'll either be an alcoholic blond. . .
. . .chasing after 20-year-old boys. . .
. . .or I'll end up like my mom!
How's it going?
Okay, except I broke up with Roger.
Yeah, right!
What happened?
I don't know. I mean. . . .
He's a good person. . .
. . .and he can be really sweet.
And in some ways,
I think he is so right for me.
It's just. . . .
I hate that guy!
What's going on?
Clear the tracks for the boobie
payback express.
Next stop, Rachel Greene.
Joey, what the hell were you doing?
Sorry, wrong boobies!
Hello, Joey!
Hello, dear!
www.tvsubtitles.net